Enter.
So you've come.
Do you know why you were summoned?
Yes, my lord.
Then what of your connections
to Prince Ravisel?
I have cut ties with him.
You were unaware of the discord between
the royal family and the spirits.
I appreciate that you can't have imagined
what you did to be problematic.
However, because of your actions,
the royal family is now after Ellen.
Ellen told me to have a word with you...
Apparently, until I do,
she has no intention of speaking to me.
Do you understand why Ellen burned
the prince's letter without reading it?
Never mind what it said.
Now there's no evidence
it was really from His Highness,
or even that you delivered it
to Ellen in the first place.
Milady has saved me, hasn't she?
First my father saves you, and now
you're indebted to my daughter.
My deepest apologies.
I'm restoring you as Sauvel's guard.
What?!
Did you not hear me?
I-I did, my lord.
However, I still can't fully trust you.
I'll be keeping my eye on you for a while.
Yes, my lord.
Be grateful to Ellen.
Alberto!
Lord Barvel!
I'll...
GODDESS VÁR'S CONDEMNATION
Lady Ellen, would you like
me to refill your drink?
Thank you, Pawpaw! Yes, please!
Ellen!
Lord Rovel.
Nothing?! Are you ignoring me, Ellen?
Did you speak with Alberto?
Yes. I've lifted his suspension.
So please at least look at me!
Could you please forgive your dear father?!
Father.
Ellen!
I think you should be more clear
with the people around you
about what will and won't cause issues.
Humans and spirits have
different values, after all.
True...
It's wrong of you to blame Uncle Alberto
after neglecting to do so!
Yes, ma'am.
As long as you're reflecting
on your mistakes, you're good.
There. There.
Ellen!
My, my. I can't tell which of you
is the parent here anymore.
I understand that you're
thinking of me, Father.
But if you're going to use me as bait,
please let me know in advance.
I couldn't help taking it out on you.
It was a horrible punishment.
Now, we can think of how to deal
with Mr. Blackheart together, can't we?
Mr. Blackheart?
I mean Prince Ravisel, who is purely
evil at heart, sinister, and spiteful.
What a fitting description!
Just so you know, you are too, Father.
How?!
That's awful!
That's really awful of you, Ellen!
Father, haven't you had enough?
Oh, come on. Just a little longer.
Now, now! Let us lighten the mood
a bit and have fun today!
Very good, Pawpaw!
Okay, let us show Lady Ellen our skills as
those who serve the knights on a daily basis!
Understood!
Nine, ten! Are you ready?!
Come and find us, milady!
Now then, where could you all be hiding?
I'm going to find everyone right away!
Huh?
Not here.
How about here?!
Not here either.
I can't find them...
Oh, drat! How could I let this happen?
This simply won't do.
Pawpaw!
Your pawpaw shall assist you.
Ah!
There!
Found you!
That's our Lady Ellen!
All right! Your father's going to help too!
Right here!
Here!
Over there!
How's that, Ellen?
I'm playing with Pawpaw and the others.
Father, please don't butt in!
I'm sorry, Ellen!
Could we play one more time?
Why, of course!
Miss Ellen, can I please join in too?
Miss Ellen! Hey! Please, I beg you!
It's interesting to see so many
unexpected sides of Lord Rovel.
Indeed. Moreover, Ellen's presence
here brings such joy.
Here I come!
Grammie, can I come over and play again?
Of course you can, Ellen!
Come anytime.
I will!
You too, Pawpaw!
You're always welcome here.
Thank you very much!
Uncle Alberto.
I'm so glad.
If anything happens, be sure to consult
Uncle Sauvel about it, okay?
Thank you very much. I shall
never forget your kindness.
You're overreacting.
Hardly.
At the very least, I want
to be able to convey my gratitude.
Okay then.
My!
What about me?
Ellen doesn't do well with beards, so...
Oh man.
Ellen.
Now, your father has a few more
things to talk about with Sauvel,
so would you mind going on home without me?
Okay! Oh, and Uncle Sauvel!
Our first order of business
is what to do with this.
How about using the suggested mine?
We could. However,
we'll need to look into it first.
True enough.
Either way, you really saved me here.
You spared our house from ruin
during my time as head of the family.
Ever since you came back, Brother...
It's like I've been on a lucky streak.
It's more that things have been
wrong until now, Your Grace.
Besides that, Sauvel...
Why don't you hurry and invite your
beloved and your daughter here?
Even Mother's curious.
I also believe that's a fine idea.
So, who is this woman you fell in love with?
About that...
She's the poster girl for an eatery
in town. Her name is Aria.
Our daughter's name is Rafilia.
She's about the same age as Ellen.
Oh?
I used to dine there
with a few of the knights, and...
She treated me kindly.
Then please bring Lady Aria
to the house as soon as possible.
Why in such a hurry?
At present, Lady Ellen is the only
heir to the Vankreift family.
However, it is her duty to one day take
Lady Origin's place as spirit queen.
We must make certain the royal family knows
the Vankreift family has a legitimate heir.
Once Ravisel ascends to the throne,
he may well issue a royal decree
forcing his son on Ellen.
You're right.
Normally, as a divorcé, I wouldn't be allowed
to marry for another three years.
The royal family has made an exception
due to the incident with Agiel,
so we can move with haste, but...
What is there to ponder?
You mustn't keep your
love waiting any longer.
Sauvel, bring her and your
daughter here tomorrow.
Understood.
Rovel and the spirit queen's daughter, huh?
Aria! Rafilia! You've made it.
Darling.
Brother, let me introduce you.
This is Aria and my daughter, Rafilia.
I am Sauvel's older brother, Rovel.
Brother dearest...
Please take good care of my brother.
Y-Yes, my lord!
Now then, let me show you around.
Aria?
Ah, coming!
Oh, that's very delicious!
Thank you very much.
It seems Aria will only be
inviting her relatives, so...
Wow!
Oh, Rafilia! Did you decide on your dress?
Uh-huh!
I'm glad to hear that.
It looks like Father is really helping
out Uncle Sauvel.
Good, good.
No, there's nothing good about this, Ellen.
Look! Look at what's happening!
Oh my, my...
But isn't this also helping Uncle?
Ori, Ellen, I'm home.
Huh? Ori, has something upset you?
She's sulking because you were drinking
with women hanging all over you, Father.
What?!
No! Um, uh, that upset me too, you know?!
Father, you reek of alcohol!
Ori! I'm sorry. I tried running from them...
I was watching, so I know.
Then...
You've been going out drinking a lot lately.
I'm really sorry, Ori!
From now on, I'll stay
with you as much as possible!
Hmph, really?
Yeah! I promise!
Really, really?
Really, really, really!
I'm turning in first.
Hold on! There's something I want
to talk to both of you about.
Sauvel's wedding date has been decided.
Most likely, the royal family will attend.
I'm sorry to ask this, Ellen,
but would you mind sitting it out?
That's fine. I do not wish
to meet Mr. Blackheart.
Wait, so I'm allowed to attend?
I need let people to know that I'm married.
I see.
Though I'd rather other men didn't
see how beautiful you are, Ori...
Oh my.
Well then, good night!
I see. So the royal family plans
to attend after all, huh?
They have some nerve to come,
especially after what happened with Agiel.
Well, you'll have to show off your
happiness to the fullest at the wedding.
Yes.
Brother, will Ellen be...
Yeah. I'm sorry, but she'll
have to sit this one out.
I see. I'm certain Mother and Roren
will be disappointed.
However, it would be best for Ellen not to come.
I'm glad we're on the same page.
Come in.
Darling, I've brought some tea.
What happened to Roren?
I asked him if I could step in
and wouldn't take no for an answer.
I'm always telling you...
You don't have to do all of this.
You mustn't take away their jobs.
I'm sorry. I wanted to do it just this once.
B-Brother dearest, have some tea.
Oh, thank you.
Here you go.
Thank you. You still have preparations
to make for tomorrow, don't you?
You can go now.
Huh? All right...
Say, Ellen, sweetie...
Between burning the world to a crisp
and plunging it into the ocean,
which do you think is better?
Mother, please calm down!
That woman is Uncle Sauvel's bride!
There's no way anything will
happen between her and Father!
But... she is sort of beautiful, isn't she?
Compared to you, Mother,
she's perfectly plain!
Ellen, dear, is your mother
winning this battle?
A landslide victory, for sure!
Thank you!
It's just that she's been
staring at him all this time.
Yeah. I'm sure Father's noticed too
and doesn't want to get involved with her.
You're right.
Oh, they've arrived.
Yes, they're here.
Wow! Father, you look handsome!
Mother, you look lovely!
Thank you.
Okay, we'll see you later.
Listen carefully, Ellen.
You mustn't come no matter what, okay?
Okay!
Brother dearest! Oh...
Could this be your...
Sorry I haven't been able
to introduce you two sooner.
This is my wife, Ori.
Nice to meet you.
Oh dear. She looks intimidated by Mother.
I hope that this will stop her
from looking at Father like that...
This is my daughter, Rafilia.
N-Nice to meet you.
You look the same age as my daughter.
I do hope you'll be friends.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Ori, take a look. It's the royal family.
That's King Ravisel, who took the throne,
and Queen Lalar,
followed by First Prince Gadiel,
Second Prince Rasel, and First Princess Ciel.
The first prince seems rather clever.
Oh, it's not just Mr. Blackheart.
These people have that black
stuff coming out of them too.
Do you vow to love one another
in sickness and in health?
I do.
I do...
Now, please sign the marriage certificate.
What happened? Are you all right?
Y-Yes... I'm sorry for the sudden reaction.
- No, it's all right, but...
- Dear.
Yeah.
There's no doubt that was
Goddess Vár's condemnation!
Mr. Blackheart noticed it too!
What should we do?!
If other people find out,
the marriage will be deemed invalid.
If that were to happen,
rumors would spread
that the Vankreift family has been
forsaken by the goddess.
There has to be a way to distract from this!
I know!
Are you sure you're all right?
Atomic number 6...
Diamond!
How beautiful.
This is...
As expected of a Vankreift family wedding!
A blessing from the goddess!
What's going on?
Could it be that Brother
asked the spirits for this?
So pretty...
Don't tell me it was Ellen...
Did it work out okay?
Oh, looks like Father and Mother
figured me out.
Amazing, isn't it, Gadiel?
This family has been blessed by the spirits.
The spirits?
It seems like everything's good,
so I'd better head home now...
TRANSLATION: YUKARI MURASE-LOUDEN
EDITING: RILEY DALTON
QUALITY CHECK: ASHLEY BARBOZA
TRANSLATION CHECK: ELIZABETH ELLIS